[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 27]
-Beat him! He deserves to die! -Shameless!
-Exactly! -Screw him!
You shameless wretch!
-He deserves to die! Hit him! -Shame on you!
-That's him! -Shameless wretch!
Zheng Yi,
Tell me—
Do I have to accept getting old?
Master,
You should never think that way.
If you do,
It will play right into their hands.
I, Zheng Yuan,
Have served as an official at the imperial court for decades,
Yet it was the first time
I had ever
Experienced that.
Master,
They just don't understand you!
But there will always be
Someone who does in this world!
Don't take it to heart.
Master Zheng Tao
Wrote to you a while ago, didn't he?
I think
Maybe we should return to Jing City,
So you can rest for a while.
You may get up.
Grandfather,
What happened outside?
What's all that fuss about?
Is Fan Yun
Doing alright?
Nine Cities is in danger.
The nobles are in trouble.
Our Zheng family is facing a crisis.
It has come to this point,
And you're still thinking about Fan Yun?
Grandfather, you care about the world,
But what have you gotten in return?
Nothing but the Governor's resentment
And the people's hatred.
Shi...
In a place as big as Nine Cities,
Sometimes you need
A so-called villain.
Tough and drastic measures are
Necessary to ensure its survival.
Ordinary people can
Easily let their emotions get the better of them.
Sometimes,
They need to be ruled with an iron fist.
I'm sacrificing myself
For the greater good of Nine Cities!
Everyone wants to be a saint,
Be a good guy,
And make everyone happy.
If we do that...
If we do that,
It'll lead to nothing
But terrible disaster.
Please forgive my bluntness.
Go ahead.
You are wrong, Grandfather.
Because it's just not worth it.
You brat!
Who says it's not worth it?
Shi...
From today on,
I can't keep you here anymore.
You're beyond my control.
You literally are...
Young Master Shi,
Are you alright?
Uncle Yi.
Where is my grandfather?
Master asked me to escort you back to your room.
Is he still mad at me?
Master
Just couldn't swallow his pride to come over.
I knew that
Grandfather wouldn't truly hold it against me.
I'm well aware of the purpose
Of your visit.
And I also understand
All your painstaking efforts.
Come on.
Let's have another drink.
Cheers.
Zheng.
I'll only drink this
If you admit that you are really getting
Senile and muddle-headed.
I admit it.
Cheers.
Only if you two
Stop being so stubborn
Will I drink this.
I promise you.
Zheng,
After the epidemic in Yong City,
I actually have growing confidence
In the young Governor and Fan Yun.
And Tian Xing—
He
Has also shown us
That the national selection exam is indeed beneficial to Nine Cities
In selecting more and better talents.
These youngsters
Have our style when we were young.
Not bad!
They're really not bad, Zheng!
We three old guys
Should start planning for the future.
How about this?
After we're done drinking tonight,
Let's go
See the world together!
Well, actually,
I'd rather go to the fields,
Farm, fish,
And live a carefree and leisurely life.
How wonderful that would be.
What's the fun in that?
Okay, good.
It's up to you.
Up to you.
-Cheers. -Cheers.
There will eventually be
An end.
Let's drink to that.
Drink up.
Okay...
Continue.
Lyu!
Lord Fan, you may get out of here now.
Now?
We've got a message from the Residence,
Saying that the Governor is not doing well.
You are requested to go over immediately.
What happened to the Governor?
Lord Tian!
Please come with me to the Qi Residence!
The Governor is in critical condition!
What?
The Governor urgently summons you.
The Governor urgently summons you!
The Governor orders you to go to the Residence at once.
Dark Wolf Token.
Dark Wolf?
The Dark Wolf who once saved me?
He's amazing.
He's not
Usually that amazing.
Anyway, just remember that
There are multiple Dark Wolves.
The Wolves of Wind he leads
Served as the late governor's secret bureau.
Once you show the token,
They'll execute
Every order without fail.
If something happens
That neither of us can handle,
Just take it to find Hu Die.
And she'll find the Dark Wolves.
What happened to the Governor?
I really have no idea.
Did something critical happen?
I was also called over here all of a sudden.
I'm wondering how the Governor is doing.
Lord Tian,
Didn't they say earlier today that he was getting better
And only needed to rest?
How come he suddenly took a turn for the worse?
I was also called over here suddenly.
I haven't seen the Governor yet.
[Hall of Political Affairs]
Lord Fan,
This way, please.
Tian Xing?
Fan Yun?
Why
Are you all here?
Why are you locking us up here?
Who exactly are you?
Where is the Governor?
How is the Governor doing?
Why did he close the door?
-Yeah, why? -I don't know.
What's going on here?
Oh, no.
We fell into a trap!
-A trap? -This is a trap?
What? How...
-Lord Zheng. -Lord Zheng.
By orders from above,
The Governor is ill and needs rest;
No one is allowed to disturb him.
Do you even dare to stop me?
This is my duty.
Please don't blame me, Lord Zheng.
I have the Supervisor's Token.
I am here to send medicine to the Governor.
Understood!
Your Excellency.
Your Excellency?
I entered the Residence in the middle of the night
And disturbed your sleep.
Please forgive me, Your Excellency.
Elder Zheng, what brings you here
So late at night?
There is an urgent document
For you to sign, Your Excellency.
Elder Zheng, you want me to admit
The failure of the national selection exam,
Abolish it,
And even swear in the name of the Governor of Nine Cities,
Without going back on my word?
Exactly.
After you sign it,
I will announce it to the public immediately.
By then,
The nobles
Will definitely feel grateful to you, Your Excellency.
However,
If you go back on your word again, Your Excellency,
The Nine Noble Families
Will absolutely not tolerate
Their dignity being trampled upon again.
And even the common people
Will never
Believe you anymore, Your Excellency.
Elder Zheng, you are really efficient and thoughtful.
You've even drafted this letter of self-condemnation for me.
Please sign it, Your Excellency.
Lord Zhang.
Attendant Wei?
The Governor has ordered us to open the gate.
What's going on today?
So many lords just entered the Residence.
They were all in a hurry.
Nothing.
You just need to open the gate.
This is the Governor's token.
Can you bear the consequences
Of delaying any important matter?
Open the gate!
I will pick it up every time
You throw it away, Your Excellency.
I will wait
Until you calm down
And sign it.
Please sign it, Your Excellency.
Guards!
Escort Lord Zheng out!
Please sign it, Your Excellency.
Zheng Yuan,
Do you know what you're doing is treason?
Please forgive me, Your Excellency.
I have no other choice.
Once you sign the letter of self-condemnation,
I am willing to bear all the consequences.
What if I insist on not signing?
Are you going to kill me today?
Your Excellency, you are the only one left carrying
The Qi family's bloodline in Nine Cities.
I have no intention of treason,
But today, Your Excellency, you
Have lost your direction.
By order
Of the late governor, I am responsible
For assisting you in political affairs.
I can no longer just stand by
And see you, Your Excellency, be deceived by sycophants
Without doing anything.
When necessary,
I must
Eliminate the root of the problem.
I once thought
You would observe Fan Yun and the others
And eventually change your attitude.
Why are you so stubborn, Elder Zheng?
You are too involved to see clearly, Your Excellency!
I watched you grow up,
So I can see things clearly.
Were it not for the slander of Fan Yun,
Tian Xing,
And others,
You would
Certainly not be so blindly obstinate now!
I see.
What did you do...
What did you do to Fan Yun and the others?
Do you want me to suffer agony worse than death?
You are so wrong, Your Excellency.
What I seek is
A long-term grand plan for Nine Cities.
I'm just asking you one question.
Where is Fan Yun right now?
Right now,
Fan Yun also has
A letter of resignation
In front of her.
Even if you don't sign this,
Once Fan Yun and the other selection exam officials
Sign the letters of resignation,
The national selection exam
Will eventually
Fizzle out.
Sign it.
None of them can be opened.
How is it?
It won't open. Still won't open.
We can't get out.
Fan Yun,
It seems we're trapped inside.
Tian Xing, look.
The people trapped here are
All civilian officials from this selection exam.
-Yeah. -Indeed.
Who told you the Governor is critically ill,
And who told you to come here?
He... He was in our official uniform,
Holding a document with the Supervisor's seal,
So we all
Followed him here.
Yes, that's exactly what happened.
Yeah, me, too.
This is indeed fishy.
If this person got the news
In the middle of the night like us,
Why would he
Specifically wear an official uniform to inform us?
Seeing him in an official uniform
With the Supervisor's seal,
And hearing the news
Of the Governor's critical condition,
Any official would follow along,
I believe.
Lady Fan Yun.
Zheng Yi?
Why are you in an official uniform?
Here we meet again.
Was it
You who did it?
You tricked us into coming here?
Tricked?
I wouldn't say that.
However,
It was indeed my doing.
Where is the Governor?
How is His Excellency doing?
His Excellency is
Currently safe and sound.
"Currently"?
What do you mean?
Could it be...
Could it be that
You're planning to hurt His Excellency?
Lady Fan,
I would never dare to bear
Such a heinous charge.
However, Lord Fan,
It's not hard to see His Excellency
If you want to.
Before you do,
There is a small matter
For you, Lady Fan Yun
And everyone else,
To handle.
-What matter? -What is it?
I don't know. Do you?
This is...
Letter of resignation?
I see.
So you want us
To voluntarily give up our positions
And never serve as an official ever again.
In your dreams.
Bring ink and brushes for the lords.
Yes.
Don't bother.
Just give up on this idea.
We won't sign it.
Lady Fan Yun,
I don't want to make things difficult for you.
But as you also know,
We both serve our respective masters,
Each performing our own duties.
How about we talk nicely
And save some dignity
For each other?
"Serve our respective masters"?
You're blindly loyal,
And you guys are rebelling, you know?
Lady Fan Yun!
We don't need your lecture!
I, Zheng Yi,
Have lived most of my life.
I had followed my master
Even before you were born.
I've been through wars,
Famines,
And prosperous times!
I witnessed Nine Cities
Getting better little by little!
My master has worked hard
For Nine Cities his whole life.
He is the most loyal subject
Of Nine Cities!
But you guys
Want to burn bridges
And ruin my master's reputation!
You are truly ambitious
And deserve to die!
You...
But Zheng Yi,
Has it ever occurred to you
That what Lord Zheng is doing right now
Is exactly going to ruin Nine Cities and the cause
He's fought for his whole life?
My master said,
"Let history judge
Whether I'm right or wrong."
Lady Fan Yun,
You have to sign
This document today,
Whether you
Like it or not.
You can't threaten me.
I get what I want,
And I'll die for a worthy cause.
I won't sign it.
-We won't sign it either. -We won't sign it either.
Right now,
There is also a document in front of the Governor.
Once His Excellency signs it,
The national selection exam will be a thing of the past.
What you are holding onto is
Nothing but a joke.
Lady Fan Yun,
I'm not here
To kill you guys today.
Don't make pointless sacrifices.
Zheng?
Zheng.
Zhao.
Sober up.
Wake up!
No, Zheng...
Zheng must have given us fake alcohol.
My head is
Throbbing right now.
Come on, stop throbbing.
Zheng is gone. There are only the two of us here.
And you're still throbbing.
Hey...
Where is your access badge?
Oh, no.
What do you mean?
He's going to do something crazy.
Lord Zhao, please don't go any further!
What are you doing?
How dare you block my way?
Back then,
I could kill a general among a large, strong army!
Do you think just the few of you
Can stop us today?
Normally,
We're definitely no match for you.
But it is different today.
Zhao,
How do you feel?
I'm fine!
You...
Fine.
If you want to kill me,
Go ahead!
Lady Fan Yun,
I'm sorry.
Zheng Yi,
You have nothing left to fight with.
Surrender now!
Dad,
Why is it you?
Am I cool?
Fan Yun.
Gao Ran?
Dad...
It's dangerous here! Get out of here!
Let's go.
Let's go!
-Let's go. -Let's go
-Run! -Hurry!
Elders, please go quickly.
Zhao, hurry!
We must ensure the Governor's safety!
What are you doing?
Zheng!
Zheng...